Myanmar Metrix Font 

"Myanmar TaBaung" Font is Non Standard Myanmar Unicode Font.
This is Beautiful Myanmar Zawgyi Font Style!
Support All Android Device.
you can use in Samung, Oppo, Huawei EMUI Vivo and Xiaomi(MIUI) without ROOT Access!
supported HUAWEI 6.0 Marshmallow.
supported MIUI 8++ without root!
Other phone requires root permission!
if you have any problem with this app, please contant me.